{
    "subject": "resource/The_Starting_Line",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Drive-Thru_Records",
    "human_readable": "The label of The Starting Line is Drive-Thru Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9191096425056458,
            "question": "Is The Starting Line still active under the Drive-Thru Records label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8488806486129761,
            "question": "What record label is associated with The Starting Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7417653203010559,
            "question": "What is the history of the Drive-Thru Records label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6668060421943665,
            "question": "Are there any other bands besides The Starting Line on Drive-Thru Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46333029866218567,
            "question": "Name a band that was signed to Drive-Thru Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4464247226715088,
            "question": "Where can you find more information about Drive-Thru Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44071435928344727,
            "question": "Are there any famous albums released by bands under Drive-Thru Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.412606805562973,
            "question": "Who released the music under Drive-Thru Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4069000780582428,
            "question": "What genre of music is often associated with Drive-Thru Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3325352370738983,
            "question": "What impact did Drive-Thru Records have on music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of The Starting Line is Drive-Thru Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5462_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is often associated with Drive-Thru Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5462_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who released the music under Drive-Thru Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5462_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous albums released by bands under Drive-Thru Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5462_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5462_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Bands that have achieved notable success during or after their time on the label include Halifax, Allister, New Found Glory, Fenix TX, Midtown, Finch, The Starting Line, Something Corporate, The Early November, Senses Fail, and Hellogoodbye.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that bands like \"The Starting Line\" have achieved notable success during or after their time on the Drive-Thru Records label. Therefore, the triple \"The label of The Starting Line is Drive-Thru Records\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}